<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid-19 Tracer</string>
    <string name="india">India</string>
    <string name="world">WORLD</string>
    <string name="bad">BAD&#160;</string>
    <string name="good">GOOD&#160;</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello!</string>
    <string name="your_name">Your Name</string>
    <string name="sign_in_heading_below_text"><![CDATA[Enter email & password to continue]]></string>
    <string name="how_are_you_feeling_at_this_moment">How are you feeling at this moment?</string>
    <string name="update_cases">Update Cases</string>
    <string name="see_details"><u>see details</u></string>
    <string name="last_updated_06_march_2020">Last updated 06 March 2020</string>
    <string name="_0000">0</string>
    <string name="your_state">Your State Name</string>
    <string name="_000">0</string>
    <string name="confirmed">Confirmed</string>
    <string name="recovered">Recovered</string>
    <string name="dead">Dead</string>
    <string name="calender">Calender</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="_011_23978076">+91–11–2397–8076</string>
    <string name="helpline_numbers">Helpline numbers :</string>
    <string name="call_now">Call Now</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="prevention">Prevention</string>
    <string name="helpful_text_quoted">\" This will pass too. Enjoy your time at home and spend quality time with your family! Things will be normal soon. \"</string>
    <string name="more_helpline_no"><u>See more...</u></string>
    <string name="stay_upto_date_with_latest_news_on_covid_19">Stay up to date with latest news on Covid-19</string>
    <string name="everything_you_need_to_know_about_covid_19">Everything you need to know about Covid-19</string>
    <string name="covid_19_realtime_spreading_in_map_view">Covid-19 Realtime Spreading in World-Map View</string>
    <string name="hospitals">Hospitals</string>
    <string name="online_scams">Online Scams</string>
    <string name="why_do_we_need_these"><u>Why do we need these?</u></string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="enter_mobile_number">&#160;Enter Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="full_name">&#160;Full Name</string>
    <string name="other_states">Other States</string>
    <string name="emergency_helpline_numbers">Emergency Helpline Numbers</string>
    <string name="_1800313444222">1800313444222</string>
    <string name="fever_des">Fever is when a human\'s body temperature goes above the normal range of  36.5 – 37.5°C or 97.7 – 99.5°F.</string>
    <string name="cough_des">A sudden, forceful hacking sound to release air and clear an irritation in the throat or airway.</string>
    <string name="shortnessOfBreath_des">Shortness of breath is an uncomfortable condition that makes it difficult to fully get air into your lungs.</string>
    <string name="achesAndPains_des">Body aches are a common symptom of many conditions. Aches can also be caused by your everyday life, especially if you stand,
        walk, or exercise for long periods of time</string>
    <string name="headache_des">A painful sensation in any part of the head, ranging from sharp to dull, that may occur with other symptoms.</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_des">Pain or irritation in the throat that can occur with or without swallowing, often accompanies infections, such as a cold or flu.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_des">Loose, watery bowel movements that may occur frequently and with a sense of urgency.</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath">Shortness \nof breath</string>
    <string name="prevention_des_text">As they say, \"Prevention is BETTER than CURE\" \n\nStay Home, Stay Safe!</string>
    <string name="handwashing_text_prevention_cardview">Wash and rub your hands properly with soup (or sanitizer) and warm water for at least 20 seconds.</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_text_prevention_cardview">Stay home and work remotely.
        If you must go out for necessities, keep 6 feet distance from others. </string>
    <string name="cough_and_sneeze_text_prevention_cardview">Use a tissue or sneeze into your elbow. Wash your hands carefully after you sneeze or cough.</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_text_prevention_cardview">Everyone should wear a cloth face cover when they have to go out in public,
        for necessities.</string>
    <string name="dont_touch_face_text_prevention_cardview">Coronavirus can live on hard surfaces for up to 72 hours.
        You can get the virus on your hands if you touch those surfaces</string>
    <string name="stay_at_home_text_prevention_cardview">Please Stay home and stay safe, it buys a little time for our
        scientists and researchers to find cure to this problem.</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_text_prevention_cardview">Clean and disinfect daily. This includes tables, doorknobs, light switches,
        handles, desks, phones, keyboards, toilets, faucets, and even sinks.</string>
    <string name="eat_healthy_text_prevention_cardview">Practicing food safety and good personal hygiene are always important,
        handwashing is especial in reducing the COVID-19 spread.</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_text_prevention_cardview">WHO recommends 150 minutes of moderate-intensity or 75 minutes of vigorous-intensity
        physical activity per week at home, with no equipment.</string>
    <string name="mail_developer">Email Address \-\-> <u>joyappsdevteam@gmail.com</u></string>
    <string name="about_us_down">\n\nDesign and Develop By \nArindam Saha\nAtul Ranjan\nJoykishan Sharma</string>

    <!--Fever Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="fever_symptom_name">Fever</string>
    <string name="fever_data_overview">Fever is also known as hyperthermia, pyrexia, or elevated temperature. It describes a body temperature that’s higher than normal.
        Fever can affect children and adults. \n\nA short-term increase in body temperature can help your body fight off illness. However, a severe fever can be a symptom of
        a serious condition that requires immediate medical attention.</string>
    <string name="fever_data_what_to_look">Fever is one of the common symptom of Coronavius cases. Recognizing a fever can enable you to get treatment and proper monitoring
        for it. Normal body temperature is typically around 98.6°F (37°C). However, the normal body temperature for each person can vary slightly.Normal body temperature
        may also fluctuate depending on the time of day. It tends to be lower in the morning and higher in the late afternoon and evening. \n\nIn general, a baby has a
        fever when their body temperature exceeds 100.4°F (38°C). A child has a fever when their temperature exceeds 99.5°F (37.5°C). An adult has a fever when their
        temperature exceeds 99–99.5°F (37.2–37.5°C).</string>
    <string name="fever_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">A mild fever can typically be treated at home. In some cases, however, a fever can be a symptom of a serious medical
        condition that requires prompt treatment. \n\nYou should take your infant to a doctor if they’re:
        \n\n\t\t•	younger than 3 months old and have a temperature exceeding 100.4°F (38°C)
        \n\n\t\t•	between 3 and 6 months old, have a temperature over 102°F (38.9°C), and seem unusually irritable, lethargic, or uncomfortable
        \n\n\t\t•	between 6 and 24 months old and have a temperature higher than 102°F (38.9°C) that lasts longer than one day
        \n\n\tYou should take your child to see a doctor if they:
        \n\n\t\t•	have a body temperature exceeding 102.2°F (39°C)
        \n\n\t\t•	have had a fever for more than three days
        \n\n\t\t•	make poor eye contact with you
        \n\n\t\t•	seem restless or irritable
        \n\n\t\t•	have recently had one or more immunizations
        \n\n\t\t•	have a serious medical illness or a compromised immune system</string>

    <!--Dry Cough Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="dry_cough_symptom_name">Dry Cough</string>
    <string name="dry_cough_data_overview">Coughing is a common reflex action that clears your throat of mucus or foreign irritants.
        While everyone coughs to clear their throat from time to time, a number of conditions can cause more frequent coughing.
        \n\n\tBasically, a dry cough is one where no mucus or phlegm is produced with the cough. Conversely, a wet cough is one filled with mucus or
        phlegm where someone can actually feel the mucus move in their bronchi or throat, mucus expectorates or leaves the chest with each (wet) cough.</string>
    <string name="dry_cough_data_what_to_look">Dry Cough is one of the common symptom of Coronavius cases. A cough that lasts for less than three weeks is an acute cough.
        Most episodes of coughing will clear up or at least significantly improve within two weeks. \n\n\tIf your cough lasts between three and eight weeks, improving by the
        end of that period, it’s considered a sub acute cough. A persistent cough that lasts more than eight weeks is a chronic cough. The most
        common cause of a cough is a respiratory tract infection, such as a cold or flu.\n\n\tRespiratory tract infections are usually caused
        by a virus and may last from a few days to a week. Infections caused by the flu may take a little longer to clear up and can sometimes
        require antibiotics.</string>
    <string name="dry_cough_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">You should see a doctor if you cough up blood or have a “barking” cough. You should also
        contact them if your cough hasn’t improved with a few days, as this could indicate something more serious like in the case coronavirus.
        This apply to for all age people, i.e. small child to elderly people. </string>

    <!--Shortness of Breath Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_symptom_name">Shortness of Breath</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_data_overview">Shortness of breath - aka, dyspnea or breathlessness - is a group of subjective sensations that suggest our
        respiratory system is not functioning well.\n\n\tThose sensations usually feel like an increased work or effort to breathe, chest tightness, and air hunger
        or "the feeling of not getting enough oxygen.</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_data_what_to_look">Shortness of breath is one of the common symptom of Coronavius cases. It is thought to be due to the development of
        pneumonia, an inflammation of the lungs linked to a coronavirus infection. The shortness of breath occurs when oxygen in the lungs doesn\'t make its way to the
        blood as a result of the viral attack.\n\n\tWhen blood carbon dioxide levels rise, a person\'s breathing rate can increase, which can lead to the sensation of
        difficulty breathing. Too much acid in the blood from an infection can also lead to the feeling of breathlessness.</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">For some diagnosed with COVID-19, shortness of breath is a more severe symptom, and can be treated
        in a hospital setting with supplemental oxygen. The extra oxygen helps increase the amount of oxygen in a patient\'s blood. In rare cases, pressurized oxygen
        through a mechanical ventilator is needed to force the oxygen through severely inflamed lungs into the blood stream.\n\n\tOverall, if you\'re worried you\'re
        experiencing shortness of breath possibly related to COVID-19, the first thing to do is try to calm down (easier said than done)—that\'s because, again,
        shortness of breath is a common symptom of anxiety. In that moment, take stock of how your body is feeling and looking overall: anxiety can also make your
        heart race, palms sweat, and pupils dilate.</string>

    <!--Aches and pains Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="aches_and_pains_symptom_name">Aches and pains</string>
    <string name="aches_and_pains_data_overview">Fatigue is a term used to describe an overall feeling of tiredness or lack of energy. It isn\’t the same as simply
        feeling drowsy or sleepy. When you\’re fatigued, you have no motivation and no energy. Being sleepy may be a symptom of fatigue, but it\’s not the same thing.
        \n\n\tFatigue is a common symptom of many medical conditions that range in severity from mild to serious</string>
    <string name="aches_and_pains_data_what_to_look">Sometime, Aches and pains is one of the symptom of Coronavius cases. Muscle fatigue is a symptom that decreases
        your muscles\' ability to perform over time. It can be associated with a state of exhaustion, often following strenuous activity or exercise. When you experience
        fatigue, the force behind your muscles\' movements decrease, causing you to feel weaker.\n\n\tTiredness, Fatigue, Body aches, muscle pain, if you experience
        this type of symptoms for more than 1-2 days, please consult your doctor immediately, this could be the early sign of Covid-19 or Coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="aches_and_pains_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">You should make an appointment with your doctor if you\’re feeling fatigued and you:
        \n\n\t•	can\’t think of anything that might account for your fatigue
        \n\n\t•	have a higher-than-normal body temperature
        \n\n\t•	have experienced unexplained weight loss
        \n\n\t•	feel very sensitive to colder temperatures
        \n\n\t•	regularly have trouble falling or staying asleep
        \n\n\t•	believe you may be depressed
        \n\nIf you\’ve made efforts to address the most common lifestyle causes, such as lack of rest, poor eating habits, and stress, without success, and your fatigue
        has continued for two weeks or more, make an appointment with your doctor.\n\nIn some cases, your fatigue might be caused by a serious medical condition.
        Go to the hospital immediately if you experience fatigue along with any of the following symptoms:
        \n\n\t•	rectal bleeding
        \n\n\t•	vomiting blood
        \n\n\t•	severe headache
        \n\n\t•	pain in your chest area
        \n\n\t•	feelings of faintness
        \n\n\t•	irregular heartbeat
        \n\n\t•	shortness of breath
        \n\n\t•	severe pain in your abdominal, back, or pelvic region</string>

    <!--Headache Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="headache_symptom_name">Headache</string>
    <string name="headache_data_overview">A headache is a very common condition that causes pain and discomfort in the head, scalp, or neck. It\’s estimated that 7 in 10
        people have at least one headache each year.\n\n\tA headache isn\'t a common symptom of the virus, but about 14% of people infected with coronavirus have
        experienced it</string>
    <string name="headache_data_what_to_look">Sometime, headache is one of the symptom of Coronavius cases. A headache can be caused by many factors related to the
        coronavirus, such as the physical discomfort of constant coughing and a stuffy sinus. \n\n\tEven frequent nose blowing can cause a headache, a lack of sleep,
        not eating properly, and failing to stay hydrated can also lead to headache. </string>
    <string name="headache_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">Headaches can sometimes be mild, but in many cases, they can cause severe pain that makes it difficult to concentrate
        at work and perform other daily activities. Luckily, most headaches can be managed with medication and lifestyle changes. \n\n\tHowever, if you have COVID-19 or
        suspect you might have it, and you\'re in any doubt about which pain relief meds to take for headache, ask your doctor to be on the safe side.\n\n\tBeyond that,
        try to eat plenty of nutritious foods, keep your fluid intake up, and getas much rest as possible.</string>

    <!--Running Nose Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="running_nose_symptom_name">Running Nose</string>
    <string name="running_nose_data_overview">Stuffy nose is a term often used to refer to obstruction to the flow of air in and out of the nose, while runny nose refers
        to a discharge (fluid) coming from the nasal passages. This is often a watery, clear liquid but may be thicker and viscous. Both stuffy and runny nose are associated
        with inflammation and swelling (congestion) of the inner lining of the nasal passages and sinuses.</string>
    <string name="running_nose_data_what_to_look">Running nose is one of the rare symptom of Coronavius cases, A stuffy or congested nose occurs when the tissues lining it
        become swollen. The swelling is due to inflamed blood vessels. The problem may also include nasal discharge or \"runny nose\". If excess mucus runs down the back of
        your throat (postnasal drip), it may cause a cough or sore throat. \n\n\tIt common happens because of common cold, Nasal congestion, also called a stuffy nose,
        is often a symptom of another health problem such as a sinus infection.</string>
    <string name="running_nose_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">If a person feels congestion or experiences a runny nose these could be early symptoms of a possible COVID-19
        infection. If you have any of these symptoms in your nose with a new and persistent cough or fever, it\’s integral to monitor these symptoms and to self-isolate.
        \n\n\tAlso inform your doctor if it lasts longer than one week, it\’s a symptom of an underlying health issue or may be covid-19.</string>

    <!--Sore Throat Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="sore_throat_symptom_name">Sore Throat</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_data_overview">A sore throat is a painful, dry, or scratchy feeling in the throat. Pain in the throat is one of the most common symptoms.
        It accounts for more than 13 million visits to doctor\’s offices each year. \n\n\tSore throat can have causes that aren\'t due to underlying disease. Examples
        include overuse of voice, a burn from hot food, very dry mouth or sleeping with the mouth open. \n\n\tMost sore throats are caused by infections, or by environmental
        factors like dry air. Although a sore throat can be uncomfortable, it\’ll usually go away on its own.</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_data_what_to_look">The symptoms of a sore throat can vary depending on what caused it. A sore throat can feel:
        \n\n\t•	scratchy
        \n\n\t•	burning
        \n\n\t•	raw
        \n\n\t•	dry
        \n\n\t•	tender
        \n\n\t•	irritated
        \n\nIt may hurt more when you swallow or talk. Your throat or tonsils might also look red. Sometimes, white patches or areas of pus will form on the tonsils.
        These white patches are more common in strep throat than in a sore throat caused by a virus. Along with the sore throat, you can have symptoms like:
        \n\n\t•	nasal congestion
        \n\n\t•	runny nose
        \n\n\t•	sneezing
        \n\n\t•	cough
        \n\n\t•	fever
        \n\n\t•	chills
        \n\n\t•	swollen glands in the neck
        \n\n\t•	hoarse voice
        \n\n\t•	body aches
        \n\n\t•	headache
        \n\n\t•	trouble swallowing
        \n\n\t•	appetite loss</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">If you have symptoms of coronavirus, even if they are mild, you must stay at home. Do not visit a hospital or pharmacy.
        get in contact with your doctor or call helpline Number. \n\n\tIf you live in the same household, or have been in contact, with someone who has symptoms, you must
        also self-isolate. You should self-isolate for a period of 14 days, as this is how long it can take to display symptoms of coronavirus. \n\n\tReport your doctor
        time to time.</string>

    <!--Diarrhea Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="diarrhea_symptom_name">Diarrhea</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_data_overview">While we are focused on cough and fever as the initial signs of COVID-19, it’s also important to be aware that abdominal pain,
        vomiting and diarrhea could precede respiratory symptoms in some people. New Study Says Digestive Issues May Be Common With Coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_data_what_to_look">The digestive problems are common overall and don\'t necessarily mean that a person has COVID-19. But if Diarrhea continuous
    more than 5-6 days, contact your doctor for diagnosis.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">Sick immediate help if you experience any of these symptoms for more than 5-6 days. The digestive symptoms tended to
        seek health care later than those with respiratory symptoms, an average of 16 days from the start of their symptoms, compared with 11 days for those with respiratory
        symptoms, the study found. \n\n\tThose with digestive symptoms also took longer to clear the virus from their body (test negative for COVID-19), taking about 41 days
        on average, compared with 33 days for those with respiratory symptoms only.\n\n\tCall helpline Number if you need help. Otherwise stay home, stay safe. </string>
    <string name="profile">\nPROFILE</string>

    <!--Wash Hand Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_name">Wash your hands frequently</string>
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_data">Washing your hands can protect you and your loved ones. Use warm water and soap and rub your hands for at least 20 seconds.
        Work the lather to your wrists, between your fingers, and under your fingernails.</string>
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_details_topic1">How Coronavirus spreads?</string>
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_details_ans1">\t• Touching your eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands
        \n\n\t• Preparing or eat food and drinks with unwashed hands
        \n\n\t• Touching a contaminated surface or objects
        \n\n\t• Blowing your nose, cough, or sneeze into hands and then touching other people’s hands or common objects</string>
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_details_topic2">Key Times to Wash Hands</string>
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_details_ans2">\t• Before, during, and after preparing food
        \n\n\t• Before eating food
        \n\n\t• Before and after caring for someone at home who is sick with vomiting or diarrhea
        \n\n\t• Before and after treating a cut or wound
        \n\n\t• After using the toilet
        \n\n\t• After changing diapers or cleaning up a child who has used the toilet
        \n\n\t• After blowing your nose, coughing, or sneezing
        \n\n\t• After touching an animal, animal feed, or animal waste
        \n\n\t• After handling pet food or pet treats
        \n\n\t• After touching garbage</string>
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_details_topic3">Five Steps to Wash Your Hands the Right Way</string>
    <string name="wash_hand_prevention_details_ans3">\t\t• Wet your hands with clean, running water (warm or cold), turn off the tap, and apply soap.
        \n\n\t• Lather your hands by rubbing them together with the soap. Lather the backs of your hands,
        between your fingers, and under your nails.
        \n\n\t• Scrub your hands for at least 20 seconds. Need a timer? Hum the “Happy Birthday” song from beginning to end twice.
        \n\n\t• Rinse your hands well under clean, running water.
        \n\n\t• Dry your hands using a clean towel or air dry them.</string>

    <!--Social Distancing Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_name">Take social distancing seriously</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_data">Social distancing, also called “physical distancing,” means keeping space between
        yourself and other people outside of your home. To practice social or physical distancing: Stay at least 6 feet (2 meters) from other
        people. Do not gather in groups. Stay out of crowded places and avoid mass gatherings</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_details_topic1">Why practice social distancing?</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_details_ans1">COVID-19 spreads mainly among people who are in close contact (within about
        6 feet) for a prolonged period. Spread happens when an infected person coughs, sneezes, or talks, and droplets from their mouth
        or nose are launched into the air and land in the mouths or noses of people nearby. The droplets can also be inhaled into the
        lungs. Recent studies indicate that people who are infected but do not have symptoms likely also play a role in the spread of
        COVID-19.</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_details_topic2">Tips for social distancing</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_details_ans2">\t\t• If you need to shop for food or medicine at the grocery store or pharmacy,
        stay at least 6 feet away from others.
        \n\n\t• Use mail-order for medications, if possible.
        \n\n\t• Consider a grocery delivery service.
        \n\n\t• Cover your mouth and nose with a cloth face cover when around others, including when you have to go out in public,
        for example to the grocery store.
        \n\n\t• Stay at least 6 feet between yourself and others, even when you wear a face covering.
        \n\n\t• Avoid large and small gatherings in private places and public spaces, such a friend’s house, parks, restaurants,
        shops, or any other place.
        \n\n\t• Work from home when possible.
        \n\n\t• If possible, avoid using any kind of public transportation, ridesharing, or taxis.
        \n\n\t• If you are a student or parent, talk to your school about options for digital/distance learning.</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_details_topic3"> </string>
    <string name="social_distancing_prevention_details_ans3"> </string>

    <!--Cover your mouth Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_name">Cover your mouth and nose when you cough and sneeze</string>
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_data">Sneezing or coughing with no hands won\’t just embarrass your parents,
        it\’ll likely shoot germs over 10 feet to other surfaces, where they can live for weeks until someone comes in contact
        with them. It makes you rethink touching those elevator buttons or picking up magazines in a waiting room.Sneezes and
        coughs spread all kinds of germs, and it’s best to cover them the correct way to prevent spreading illness.</string>
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_details_topic1">To help stop the spread</string>
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_details_ans1">\t\t• Cover your mouth and nose with a tissue when you cough or sneeze.
        \n\n\t• Put your used tissue in a waste basket.
        \n\n\t• If you don’t have a tissue, cough or sneeze into your upper sleeve, not your hands. Although it isn\’t the best way to
        keep germs from traveling, some experts suggest it is better than using your hands</string>
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_details_topic2">If you feel like you got symptoms</string>
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_details_ans2">\t\t• Wear clean facemask

        \n\n\t• Self-Isolate yourself
        \n\n\t• Call your doctor or call helpline number
        \n\n\t• avoid touching stuffs around you
        \n\n\t• clean your hand frequently</string>
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_details_topic3"> </string>
    <string name="cover_your_mouth_prevention_details_ans3"> </string>

    <!--Wear Facemask Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_name">Wear facemask when getting into crowded place</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_data">People should wear nonsurgical cloth face coverings when they go out in public during the
        COVID-19 pandemic. Headlines of the new coronavirus creeping its way across the globe is a good reminder that the
        best way to protect our communities from widespread transmission of illness is to practice good basic hygiene every day</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_details_topic1">How to Wear a Cloth Face Covering</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_details_ans1">Cloth face coverings should—
        \n\n\t• fit snugly but comfortably against the side of the face
        \n\n\t• be secured with ties or ear loops
        \n\n\t• include multiple layers of fabric
        \n\n\t• allow for breathing without restriction
        \n\n\t• be able to be laundered and machine dried without damage or change to shape</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_details_topic2">If you feel like you got symptoms</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_details_ans2">\t\t• Wear clean facemask
        \n\n\t• Self-Isolate yourself
        \n\n\t• Call your doctor or call helpline number
        \n\n\t• avoid touching stuffs around you
        \n\n\t• clean your hand frequently</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_details_topic3">Points to Remember while wearing mask</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_prevention_details_ans3">\t\t• Cloth face coverings should not be placed on young children under age 2,
        anyone who has trouble breathing, or is unconscious, incapacitated or otherwise unable to remove the mask without assistance.
        \n\n\t• The cloth face coverings recommended are not surgical masks or N-95 respirators.  Those are critical supplies that must
        continue to be reserved for healthcare workers and other medical first responders
        \n\n\t• If you can\'t affprt to buy a decent face mask, then you can also make your own face mask at home with minimum requirements.
     Go online and watch video on \"how to make your own fask mask for Covid-19\", that should help.</string>

    <!--Avoid touching your face Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_name">Avoid touching your face</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_data">Humans have a rather unusual habit we don\’t share with many other animals, and,
        unfortunately, it makes us particularly susceptible during certain disease outbreaks – we keep touching our faces.</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_details_topic1">How virus spreads when you touch your face?</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_details_ans1">\t\t• Your eyes, nose, and mouth are the easiest paths for a virus like
        \n\n\t• SARS-CoV-2 to enter the body.
        \n\n\t• All it takes is touching these areas with your hands after you’ve come in contact with the
        disease on a surface you touched.
        \n\n\t• No matter how frequently you wash your hands, it’s not often enough to prevent passing an infection into your system.
        \n\n\t• The best preventive measure is to avoid touching your face as much as possible.</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_details_topic2">How to break this habit of touching face?</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_details_ans2">Experts say that using some simple methods will help you break
        this habit. These include using scented hand soap or sanitizer to increase awareness of where your hands are and keeping
        your hands in your lap during meetings.</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_details_topic3"> </string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_face_prevention_details_ans3"> </string>

    <!--Stay Home, Stay Safe Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_name">Stay Home, Stay Safe</string>
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_data">Governments around the world are encouraging people to stay at home to protect
        health services and save lives. People can only leave their homes to buy food, medicine.They\'re allowed to travel, but only
        to and from work if they cannot do their jobs from home. Staying at home to keep people safe can be a difficult concept to
        grasp, especially when you are feeling fit and healthy yourself.</string>
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_details_topic1">Why staying at home helps others?</string>
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_details_ans1">It can help in many ways, few of them are given below :
        \n\n\t• Deduces the chances of catching and spreading the virus.
        \n\n\t• It is very hard to know if you have Covid-19 positive in the early stages, so why not stop going out and halt the spreading.
        \n\n\t• Currently we don\'t have vaccine for this virus so we need to stay at home to minimum its spread.
        \n\n\t• If you get infect because of your carelessness, it\'s going to affect your whole family.
        \n\n\t• Staying home gives the researcher little time to find a vaccine for this deadly virus.help them by staying home.</string>
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_details_topic2">How to escape boredom when staying at home? </string>
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_details_ans2">There is lots of things to do when you feel bored, you just need to look for it.
        Few are given below :
        \n\n\t• Figure out what you really want to do.
        \n\n\t• Nuke procrastination.
        \n\n\t• Spend Quality time with your family. Trust me, they always need it.
        \n\n\t• Learn something new.
        \n\n\t• Meditate.
        \n\n\t• And many more, list is never ending.</string>
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_details_topic3"> </string>
    <string name="stay_home_stay_safe_prevention_details_ans3"> </string>

    <!--Do Some Exercise Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_name">Do Some Exercise</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_data">The COVID-19 pandemic has pushed many of us to self-isolate and practice social
        distancing, but this should not prevent us from staying active. Exercising at home and maintaining (or developing) an active
        lifestyle is an important part of keeping both your body and your mind healthy.</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_details_topic1">Indoor Exercises for Small Spaces</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_details_ans1">When we don’t have access to a gym with all its space and equipment, we
        have to improvise. Fortunately, thanks to the internet, it is now easier than ever to work out at home using resources you can
        find for free online.
        \n\n\t• Yoga
        \n\n\t• Pilates
        \n\n\t• Weight Lifting
        \n\n\t• Steps
        \n\n\t• Jump Rope</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_details_topic2">Why Exercise at all?</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_details_ans2">Keeping yourself active not only benefits you physically, but it is also
        incredibly important for keeping a healthy mental state. As quarantine times are extended across country and the rest of the
        world, it can be extremely mentally taxing for individuals who are used to daily socialisation. Suddenly being cut off from
        in-person social interactions, combined with being stuck inside all day and inactive is a recipe for lack of motivation and
        even depression.
        \n\nGetting fresh air, eating healthily, and exercising will help you tremendously until the quarantine is
         lifted.</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_details_topic3"> </string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_prevention_details_ans3"> </string>

    <!--Stay hygiene, eat healthy Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_name">Stay hygiene, eat healthy</string>
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_data">Good nutrition is crucial for health, particularly in
        times when the immune system might need to fight back. Limited access to fresh foods may compromise opportunities to continue
        eating a healthy and varied diet. It can also potentially lead to an increased consumption of highly processed foods, which tend
        to be high in fats, sugars and salt. Nonetheless, even with few and limited ingredients, one can continue eating a diet that
        supports good health.</string>
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_details_topic1">Tips to stay healthy</string>
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_details_ans1">Whether you are in quarantine or self-isolation due to COVID-19,
        you will inevitably be spending more time at home. Following general healthy living advice are the best recommendation for
        staying healthy during quarantine or self-isolation.
        \n\n\t• Eat a balanced and varied diet
        \n\n\t• Establish a routine and practice mindful eating
        \n\n\t• Keep hydrated
        \n\n\t• Practice safe food hygiene
        \n\n\t• Stay active at home
        \n\n\t• Get enough quality sleep
        \n\n\t• Get information from trustworthy sources</string>
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_details_topic2">Eat right food during this quarantine</string>
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_details_ans2">Note that these are just for your immune system boosting.Don\'t
        misunderstand these by thinking that these are the cure ingredients for covid-19.
        \n\n\t• Citrus fruits
        \n\n\t• Turmeric
        \n\n\t• Garlic
        \n\n\t• Ginger
        \n\n\t• Spinach
        \n\n\t• Yoghurt
        \n\n\t• Green Tea
        \n\n\t• Papaya
        \n\n\t• Almonds</string>
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_details_topic3"> </string>
    <string name="stay_hygiene_eat_healthy_prevention_details_ans3"> </string>

    <!-- Clean and disinfect Prevention in Detail-->
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_name">Clean and disinfect</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_data">In the era of disinfectant wipes and sprays flying off shelves because of the
        novel coronavirus, which causes the potentially severe respiratory disease, COVID-19, we\’re all a little obsessed with cleaning.
        The virus can hang out on surfaces for hours to days so keep clean those areas and surface which used and touched frequently.</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_details_topic1">Few areas were you should keep clean</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_details_ans1">Note that these areas and places may vary from home to home, so it is up to you to
        identify frequently places.
        \n\n\t• Tables (this includes your kitchen table and counter)
        \n\n\t• Hard-backed chairs (for instance, kitchen chairs around the table you eat dinner on)
        \n\n\t• Doorknobs
        \n\n\t• Light switches
        \n\n\t• Handles (eg. refrigerator handle, handles on drawers)
        \n\n\t• The sink in the kitchen and bathroom.
        \n\n\t• TV Remotes</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_details_topic2">How Often to Disinfect Your Home</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_details_ans2">Repeat this disinfecting routine on frequently touched surfaces daily,
        or more often if someone in your household is sick; the virus can survive for 16 hours on plastic surfaces.
        \n\nRemember that, keeping your kitchen surfaces as clean and home disinfected is secondary to practicing isolation
        techniques and washing your hands when you return home. That\’s your front line of prevention,</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_details_topic3"> </string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_prevention_details_ans3"> </string>
    <string name="_104">Bihar / Chhattisgarh / Goa / Gujarat / Himachal Pradesh / Jharkhand / Karnataka / Madhya Pradesh / Punjab / Sikkim / Telangana / Uttarakhand</string>
    <string name="about_us_text">Thank you very much for downloading this App. If you have any Suggestion or Query, Feel free to mail us. You can mail us at</string>
    <string name="team_name">Joy Apps Developers Team</string>
    <string name="temporary_text">Hi, It Looks like this Page is not ready yet.\nWe are Sorry for that.\n\nOur Developer Team is
        constantly working. We will fix this Page very soon in the Upcoming Updates.\n\nThank you for understanding.\n\n
        <![CDATA[You can reach out to us through this mail —> ]]></string>
    <string name="mail_us_temporary"><u>joyappsdevteam@gmail.com</u></string>
    <string name="symptom_top_cardview_text">The symptoms may appear between 2–14 days after exposure.\n\nStay home,
        get in touch with your doctor or call helpline if you catch any symptom</string>
    <string name="myth_busters">Myth Busters</string>
    <string name="related_videos">Related Videos</string>
    <string name="healthy_parenting">Healthy Parenting</string>
    <string name="hospital_list_cardview_text">Before taking any final decision, we recommend you to Call on helpline Number and discuss your matter.</string>

</resources>
