<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid-19 Tracer</string>
    <string name="india">INDIA</string>
    <string name="world">WORLD</string>
    <string name="bad">BAD&#160;</string>
    <string name="good">GOOD&#160;</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello!</string>
    <string name="your_name">Your Name</string>
    <string name="how_are_you_feeling_at_this_moment">How are you feeling at this moment?</string>
    <string name="update_cases">Update Cases</string>
    <string name="see_details"><u>see details</u></string>
    <string name="last_updated_06_march_2020">Last updated 06 March 2020</string>
    <string name="_0000">0</string>
    <string name="your_state">Your State Name</string>
    <string name="_000">0</string>
    <string name="confirmed">Confirmed</string>
    <string name="recovered">Recovered</string>
    <string name="dead">Dead</string>
    <string name="calender">Calender</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="_011_23978076">+91–11–2397–8076</string>
    <string name="helpline_numbers">Helpline numbers :</string>
    <string name="call_now">Call Now</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="prevention">Prevention</string>
    <string name="helpful_text_quoted">\" This will pass too. Enjoy your time at home and spend quality time with your family! Things will be normal soon. \"</string>
    <string name="more_helpline_no"><u>See more...</u></string>
    <string name="stay_upto_date_with_latest_news_on_covid_19">Stay up to date with latest news on Covid-19</string>
    <string name="everything_you_need_to_know_about_covid_19">Everything you need to know about Covid-19</string>
    <string name="covid_19_realtime_spreading_in_map_view">Covid-19 Realtime Spreading in World-Map View</string>
    <string name="hospitals">Hospitals</string>
    <string name="report">Report</string>
    <string name="why_do_we_need_these"><u>Why do we need these?</u></string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="enter_mobile_number">&#160;Enter Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="full_name">&#160;Full Name</string>
    <string name="other_states">Other States</string>
    <string name="emergency_helpline_numbers">Emergency Helpline Numbers</string>
    <string name="_1800313444222">1800313444222</string>
    <string name="fever_des">Fever is when a human\'s body temperature goes above the normal range of  36.5 – 37.5°C or 97.7 – 99.5°F.</string>
    <string name="cough_des">A sudden, forceful hacking sound to release air and clear an irritation in the throat or airway.</string>
    <string name="shortnessOfBreath_des">Shortness of breath is an uncomfortable condition that makes it difficult to fully get air into your lungs.</string>
    <string name="achesAndPains_des">Body aches are a common symptom of many conditions. Aches can also be caused by your everyday life, especially if you stand,
        walk, or exercise for long periods of time</string>
    <string name="headache_des">A painful sensation in any part of the head, ranging from sharp to dull, that may occur with other symptoms.</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_des">Pain or irritation in the throat that can occur with or without swallowing, often accompanies infections, such as a cold or flu.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_des">Loose, watery bowel movements that may occur frequently and with a sense of urgency.</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath">Shortness \nof breath</string>

    <string name="fever_data_overview">Fever is also known as hyperthermia, pyrexia, or elevated temperature. It describes a body temperature that’s higher than normal.
        Fever can affect children and adults. \n\nA short-term increase in body temperature can help your body fight off illness. However, a severe fever can be a symptom of
        a serious condition that requires immediate medical attention.</string>
    <string name="fever_data_what_to_look">Recognizing a fever can enable you to get treatment and proper monitoring for it. Normal body temperature is typically around 98.6°F
        (37°C). However, the normal body temperature for each person can vary slightly.Normal body temperature may also fluctuate depending on the time of day. It tends to be
        lower in the morning and higher in the late afternoon and evening. \n\nIn general, a baby has a fever when their body temperature exceeds 100.4°F (38°C).
        A child has a fever when their temperature exceeds 99.5°F (37.5°C). An adult has a fever when their temperature exceeds 99–99.5°F (37.2–37.5°C).</string>
    <string name="fever_data_what_to_see_a_doctor">A mild fever can typically be treated at home. In some cases, however, a fever can be a symptom of a serious medical
        condition that requires prompt treatment. \n\nYou should take your infant to a doctor if they’re:
        \n\n\t\t•	younger than 3 months old and have a temperature exceeding 100.4°F (38°C)
        \n\n\t\t•	between 3 and 6 months old, have a temperature over 102°F (38.9°C), and seem unusually irritable, lethargic, or uncomfortable
        \n\n\t\t•	between 6 and 24 months old and have a temperature higher than 102°F (38.9°C) that lasts longer than one day
        \n\n\tYou should take your child to see a doctor if they:
        \n\n\t\t•	have a body temperature exceeding 102.2°F (39°C)
        \n\n\t\t•	have had a fever for more than three days
        \n\n\t\t•	make poor eye contact with you
        \n\n\t\t•	seem restless or irritable
        \n\n\t\t•	have recently had one or more immunizations
        \n\n\t\t•	have a serious medical illness or a compromised immune system
</string>
</resources>
