<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid-19 Tracer</string>
    <string name="india">INDIA</string>
    <string name="world">WORLD</string>
    <string name="bad">BAD&#160;</string>
    <string name="good">GOOD&#160;</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello!</string>
    <string name="your_name">Your Name</string>
    <string name="how_are_you_feeling_at_this_moment">How are you feeling at this moment?</string>
    <string name="update_cases">Update Cases</string>
    <string name="see_details"><u>see details</u></string>
    <string name="last_updated_06_march_2020">Last updated 06 March 2020</string>
    <string name="_0000">0</string>
    <string name="your_state">Your State Name</string>
    <string name="_000">0</string>
    <string name="confirmed">Confirmed</string>
    <string name="recovered">Recovered</string>
    <string name="dead">Dead</string>
    <string name="calender">Calender</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="_011_23978076">+91–11–2397–8076</string>
    <string name="helpline_numbers">Helpline numbers :</string>
    <string name="call_now">Call Now</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="prevention">Prevention</string>
    <string name="helpful_text_quoted">\" This will pass too. Enjoy your time at home and spend quality time with your family! Things will be normal soon. \"</string>
    <string name="more_helpline_no"><u>See more...</u></string>
    <string name="stay_upto_date_with_latest_news_on_covid_19">Stay up to date with latest news on Covid-19</string>
    <string name="everything_you_need_to_know_about_covid_19">Everything you need to know about Covid-19</string>
    <string name="covid_19_realtime_spreading_in_map_view">Covid-19 Realtime Spreading in World-Map View</string>
    <string name="hospitals">Hospitals</string>
    <string name="report">Report</string>
    <string name="why_do_we_need_these"><u>Why do we need these?</u></string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="enter_mobile_number">&#160;Enter Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="full_name">&#160;Full Name</string>
    <string name="other_states">Other States</string>
    <string name="emergency_helpline_numbers">Emergency Helpline Numbers</string>
    <string name="_1800313444222">1800313444222</string>
    <string name="fever_des">Fever is when a human\'s body temperature goes above the normal range of  36.5 – 37.5°C or 97.7 – 99.5°F.</string>
    <string name="cough_des">A sudden, forceful hacking sound to release air and clear an irritation in the throat or airway.</string>
    <string name="shortnessOfBreath_des">Shortness of breath is an uncomfortable condition that makes it difficult to fully get air into your lungs.</string>
    <string name="achesAndPains_des">Body aches are a common symptom of many conditions. Aches can also be caused by your everyday life, especially if you stand,
        walk, or exercise for long periods of time</string>
    <string name="headache_des">A painful sensation in any part of the head, ranging from sharp to dull, that may occur with other symptoms.</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_des">Pain or irritation in the throat that can occur with or without swallowing, often accompanies infections, such as a cold or flu.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_des">Loose, watery bowel movements that may occur frequently and with a sense of urgency.</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath">Shortness \nof breath</string>
    <string name="prevention_des_text">As they say, \"Prevention is BETTER than CURE\" \n\nStay Home, Stay Safe!</string>
    <string name="handwashing_text_prevention_cardview">Use warm water and soap and rub your hands for at least 20 seconds.
        Work the lather to your wrists, between your fingers, and under your fingernails.</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_text_prevention_cardview">Stay home and work remotely when possible.
        If you must go out for necessities, keep a distance of 6 feet from other people. </string>
    <string name="cough_and_sneeze_text_prevention_cardview">Use a tissue or sneeze into your elbow to keep your
        hands as clean as possible. Wash your hands carefully after you sneeze or cough, regardless.</string>
    <string name="wear_facemask_text_prevention_cardview">Everyone should wear a cloth face cover when they have to go out in public,
        for example to the grocery store or to pick up other necessities.</string>
    <string name="dont_touch_face_text_prevention_cardview">SARS-CoV-2 can live on hard surfaces for up to 72 hours.
        You can get the virus on your hands if you touch a surface like a doorknob, gas pump handle, or your cell phone.</string>
    <string name="stay_at_home_text_prevention_cardview">Please Stay home and stay safe, it buys a little time for our
        researchers to find cure to this problem. \nRemember that some people without symptoms may be able to spread virus.</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_text_prevention_cardview">Clean and disinfect daily. This includes tables, doorknobs, light switches,
        countertops, handles, desks, phones, keyboards, toilets, faucets, and even sinks.</string>
    <string name="eat_healthy_text_prevention_cardview">Practicing home food safety and good personal hygiene are always important,
        handwashing is especially critical in reducing the COVID-19 spread and should be done often.</string>
    <string name="do_some_exercise_text_prevention_cardview">WHO recommends 150 minutes of moderate-intensity or 75 minutes of vigorous-intensity
        physical activity per week. These can still be achieved even at home, with no equipment and with limited space.</string>



    <!--Fever Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="fever_symptom_name">Fever</string>
    <string name="fever_data_overview">Fever is also known as hyperthermia, pyrexia, or elevated temperature. It describes a body temperature that’s higher than normal.
        Fever can affect children and adults. \n\nA short-term increase in body temperature can help your body fight off illness. However, a severe fever can be a symptom of
        a serious condition that requires immediate medical attention.</string>
    <string name="fever_data_what_to_look">Fever is one of the common symptom of Coronavius cases. Recognizing a fever can enable you to get treatment and proper monitoring
        for it. Normal body temperature is typically around 98.6°F (37°C). However, the normal body temperature for each person can vary slightly.Normal body temperature
        may also fluctuate depending on the time of day. It tends to be lower in the morning and higher in the late afternoon and evening. \n\nIn general, a baby has a
        fever when their body temperature exceeds 100.4°F (38°C). A child has a fever when their temperature exceeds 99.5°F (37.5°C). An adult has a fever when their
        temperature exceeds 99–99.5°F (37.2–37.5°C).</string>
    <string name="fever_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">A mild fever can typically be treated at home. In some cases, however, a fever can be a symptom of a serious medical
        condition that requires prompt treatment. \n\nYou should take your infant to a doctor if they’re:
        \n\n\t\t•	younger than 3 months old and have a temperature exceeding 100.4°F (38°C)
        \n\n\t\t•	between 3 and 6 months old, have a temperature over 102°F (38.9°C), and seem unusually irritable, lethargic, or uncomfortable
        \n\n\t\t•	between 6 and 24 months old and have a temperature higher than 102°F (38.9°C) that lasts longer than one day
        \n\n\tYou should take your child to see a doctor if they:
        \n\n\t\t•	have a body temperature exceeding 102.2°F (39°C)
        \n\n\t\t•	have had a fever for more than three days
        \n\n\t\t•	make poor eye contact with you
        \n\n\t\t•	seem restless or irritable
        \n\n\t\t•	have recently had one or more immunizations
        \n\n\t\t•	have a serious medical illness or a compromised immune system</string>

    <!--Dry Cough Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="dry_cough_symptom_name">Dry Cough</string>
    <string name="dry_cough_data_overview">Coughing is a common reflex action that clears your throat of mucus or foreign irritants.
        While everyone coughs to clear their throat from time to time, a number of conditions can cause more frequent coughing.
        \n\n\tBasically, a dry cough is one where no mucus or phlegm is produced with the cough. Conversely, a wet cough is one filled with mucus or
        phlegm where someone can actually feel the mucus move in their bronchi or throat, mucus expectorates or leaves the chest with each (wet) cough.</string>
    <string name="dry_cough_data_what_to_look">Dry Cough is one of the common symptom of Coronavius cases. A cough that lasts for less than three weeks is an acute cough.
        Most episodes of coughing will clear up or at least significantly improve within two weeks. \n\n\tIf your cough lasts between three and eight weeks, improving by the
        end of that period, it’s considered a sub acute cough. A persistent cough that lasts more than eight weeks is a chronic cough. The most
        common cause of a cough is a respiratory tract infection, such as a cold or flu.\n\n\tRespiratory tract infections are usually caused
        by a virus and may last from a few days to a week. Infections caused by the flu may take a little longer to clear up and can sometimes
        require antibiotics.</string>
    <string name="dry_cough_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">You should see a doctor if you cough up blood or have a “barking” cough. You should also
        contact them if your cough hasn’t improved with a few days, as this could indicate something more serious like in the case coronavirus.
        This apply to for all age people, i.e. small child to elderly people. </string>

    <!--Shortness of Breath Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_symptom_name">Shortness of Breath</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_data_overview">Shortness of breath - aka, dyspnea or breathlessness - is a group of subjective sensations that suggest our
        respiratory system is not functioning well.\n\n\tThose sensations usually feel like an increased work or effort to breathe, chest tightness, and air hunger
        or "the feeling of not getting enough oxygen.</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_data_what_to_look">Shortness of breath is one of the common symptom of Coronavius cases. It is thought to be due to the development of
        pneumonia, an inflammation of the lungs linked to a coronavirus infection. The shortness of breath occurs when oxygen in the lungs doesn\'t make its way to the
        blood as a result of the viral attack.\n\n\tWhen blood carbon dioxide levels rise, a person\'s breathing rate can increase, which can lead to the sensation of
        difficulty breathing. Too much acid in the blood from an infection can also lead to the feeling of breathlessness.</string>
    <string name="shortness_of_breath_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">For some diagnosed with COVID-19, shortness of breath is a more severe symptom, and can be treated
        in a hospital setting with supplemental oxygen. The extra oxygen helps increase the amount of oxygen in a patient\'s blood. In rare cases, pressurized oxygen
        through a mechanical ventilator is needed to force the oxygen through severely inflamed lungs into the blood stream.\n\n\tOverall, if you\'re worried you\'re
        experiencing shortness of breath possibly related to COVID-19, the first thing to do is try to calm down (easier said than done)—that\'s because, again,
        shortness of breath is a common symptom of anxiety. In that moment, take stock of how your body is feeling and looking overall: anxiety can also make your
        heart race, palms sweat, and pupils dilate.</string>

    <!--Aches and pains Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="aches_and_pains_symptom_name">Aches and pains</string>
    <string name="aches_and_pains_data_overview">Fatigue is a term used to describe an overall feeling of tiredness or lack of energy. It isn\’t the same as simply
        feeling drowsy or sleepy. When you\’re fatigued, you have no motivation and no energy. Being sleepy may be a symptom of fatigue, but it\’s not the same thing.
        \n\n\tFatigue is a common symptom of many medical conditions that range in severity from mild to serious</string>
    <string name="aches_and_pains_data_what_to_look">Sometime, Aches and pains is one of the symptom of Coronavius cases. Muscle fatigue is a symptom that decreases
        your muscles\' ability to perform over time. It can be associated with a state of exhaustion, often following strenuous activity or exercise. When you experience
        fatigue, the force behind your muscles\' movements decrease, causing you to feel weaker.\n\n\tTiredness, Fatigue, Body aches, muscle pain, if you experience
        this type of symptoms for more than 1-2 days, please consult your doctor immediately, this could be the early sign of Covid-19 or Coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="aches_and_pains_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">You should make an appointment with your doctor if you\’re feeling fatigued and you:
        \n\n\t•	can\’t think of anything that might account for your fatigue
        \n\n\t•	have a higher-than-normal body temperature
        \n\n\t•	have experienced unexplained weight loss
        \n\n\t•	feel very sensitive to colder temperatures
        \n\n\t•	regularly have trouble falling or staying asleep
        \n\n\t•	believe you may be depressed
        \n\nIf you\’ve made efforts to address the most common lifestyle causes, such as lack of rest, poor eating habits, and stress, without success, and your fatigue
        has continued for two weeks or more, make an appointment with your doctor.\n\nIn some cases, your fatigue might be caused by a serious medical condition.
        Go to the hospital immediately if you experience fatigue along with any of the following symptoms:
        \n\n\t•	rectal bleeding
        \n\n\t•	vomiting blood
        \n\n\t•	severe headache
        \n\n\t•	pain in your chest area
        \n\n\t•	feelings of faintness
        \n\n\t•	irregular heartbeat
        \n\n\t•	shortness of breath
        \n\n\t•	severe pain in your abdominal, back, or pelvic region</string>

    <!--Headache Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="headache_symptom_name">Headache</string>
    <string name="headache_data_overview">A headache is a very common condition that causes pain and discomfort in the head, scalp, or neck. It\’s estimated that 7 in 10
        people have at least one headache each year.\n\n\tA headache isn\'t a common symptom of the virus, but about 14% of people infected with coronavirus have
        experienced it</string>
    <string name="headache_data_what_to_look">Sometime, headache is one of the symptom of Coronavius cases. A headache can be caused by many factors related to the
        coronavirus, such as the physical discomfort of constant coughing and a stuffy sinus. \n\n\tEven frequent nose blowing can cause a headache, a lack of sleep,
        not eating properly, and failing to stay hydrated can also lead to headache. </string>
    <string name="headache_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">Headaches can sometimes be mild, but in many cases, they can cause severe pain that makes it difficult to concentrate
        at work and perform other daily activities. Luckily, most headaches can be managed with medication and lifestyle changes. \n\n\tHowever, if you have COVID-19 or
        suspect you might have it, and you\'re in any doubt about which pain relief meds to take for headache, ask your doctor to be on the safe side.\n\n\tBeyond that,
        try to eat plenty of nutritious foods, keep your fluid intake up, and getas much rest as possible.</string>

    <!--Running Nose Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="running_nose_symptom_name">Running Nose</string>
    <string name="running_nose_data_overview">Stuffy nose is a term often used to refer to obstruction to the flow of air in and out of the nose, while runny nose refers
        to a discharge (fluid) coming from the nasal passages. This is often a watery, clear liquid but may be thicker and viscous. Both stuffy and runny nose are associated
        with inflammation and swelling (congestion) of the inner lining of the nasal passages and sinuses.</string>
    <string name="running_nose_data_what_to_look">Running nose is one of the rare symptom of Coronavius cases, A stuffy or congested nose occurs when the tissues lining it
        become swollen. The swelling is due to inflamed blood vessels. The problem may also include nasal discharge or \"runny nose\". If excess mucus runs down the back of
        your throat (postnasal drip), it may cause a cough or sore throat. \n\n\tIt common happens because of common cold, Nasal congestion, also called a stuffy nose,
        is often a symptom of another health problem such as a sinus infection.</string>
    <string name="running_nose_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">If a person feels congestion or experiences a runny nose these could be early symptoms of a possible COVID-19
        infection. If you have any of these symptoms in your nose with a new and persistent cough or fever, it\’s integral to monitor these symptoms and to self-isolate.
        \n\n\tAlso inform your doctor if it lasts longer than one week, it\’s a symptom of an underlying health issue or may be covid-19.</string>

    <!--Sore Throat Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="sore_throat_symptom_name">Sore Throat</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_data_overview">A sore throat is a painful, dry, or scratchy feeling in the throat. Pain in the throat is one of the most common symptoms.
        It accounts for more than 13 million visits to doctor\’s offices each year. \n\n\tSore throat can have causes that aren\'t due to underlying disease. Examples
        include overuse of voice, a burn from hot food, very dry mouth or sleeping with the mouth open. \n\n\tMost sore throats are caused by infections, or by environmental
        factors like dry air. Although a sore throat can be uncomfortable, it\’ll usually go away on its own.</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_data_what_to_look">The symptoms of a sore throat can vary depending on what caused it. A sore throat can feel:
        \n\n\t•	scratchy
        \n\n\t•	burning
        \n\n\t•	raw
        \n\n\t•	dry
        \n\n\t•	tender
        \n\n\t•	irritated
        \n\nIt may hurt more when you swallow or talk. Your throat or tonsils might also look red. Sometimes, white patches or areas of pus will form on the tonsils.
        These white patches are more common in strep throat than in a sore throat caused by a virus. Along with the sore throat, you can have symptoms like:
        \n\n\t•	nasal congestion
        \n\n\t•	runny nose
        \n\n\t•	sneezing
        \n\n\t•	cough
        \n\n\t•	fever
        \n\n\t•	chills
        \n\n\t•	swollen glands in the neck
        \n\n\t•	hoarse voice
        \n\n\t•	body aches
        \n\n\t•	headache
        \n\n\t•	trouble swallowing
        \n\n\t•	appetite loss</string>
    <string name="sore_throat_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">If you have symptoms of coronavirus, even if they are mild, you must stay at home. Do not visit a hospital or pharmacy.
        get in contact with your doctor or call helpline Number. \n\n\tIf you live in the same household, or have been in contact, with someone who has symptoms, you must
        also self-isolate. You should self-isolate for a period of 14 days, as this is how long it can take to display symptoms of coronavirus. \n\n\tReport your doctor
        time to time.</string>

    <!--Diarrhea Symptoms in Detail-->
    <string name="diarrhea_symptom_name">Diarrhea</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_data_overview">While we are focused on cough and fever as the initial signs of COVID-19, it’s also important to be aware that abdominal pain,
        vomiting and diarrhea could precede respiratory symptoms in some people. New Study Says Digestive Issues May Be Common With Coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_data_what_to_look">The digestive problems are common overall and don\'t necessarily mean that a person has COVID-19. But if Diarrhea continuous
    more than 5-6 days, contact your doctor for diagnosis.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_data_when_to_see_a_doctor">Sick immediate help if you experience any of these symptoms for more than 5-6 days. The digestive symptoms tended to
        seek health care later than those with respiratory symptoms, an average of 16 days from the start of their symptoms, compared with 11 days for those with respiratory
        symptoms, the study found. \n\n\tThose with digestive symptoms also took longer to clear the virus from their body (test negative for COVID-19), taking about 41 days
        on average, compared with 33 days for those with respiratory symptoms only.\n\n\tCall helpline Number if you need help. Otherwise stay home, stay safe. </string>
    <string name="profile">\nPROFILE</string>


</resources>
